(window["webpackJsonp"]=window["webpackJsonp"]||[]).push([["chunk-d846650e"],{"0da3":function(e,t,n){},"2e44":function(e,t,n){"use strict";n.r(t);var i=n("7a23"),s=(n("d81d"),n("7db0"),n("d3b7"),n("6422")),a=n.n(s),o=(n("9911"),n("2ca0"),n("99af"),n("ac1f"),n("5319"),n("5502")),r=n("0e54"),c=n.n(r),l=n("1e46"),d=n.n(l),u={key:0},f={class:"card",style:{"max-width":"40rem"}},b={class:"card-header"},h={class:"card-body"},m={class:"fs-5"},p=["innerHTML"],g={class:"align-middle text-center"},j={class:"btn-group float-start",role:"group"},O=["disabled","onClick"],y={key:0,class:"align-middle text-center text-success fs-5"},v={key:1,class:"text-danger fs-5"},x={key:0,class:"btn float-end btn-outline-secondary","data-bs-toggle":"collapse","data-bs-target":"#explain","aria-expanded":"false","aria-controls":"explain"},w={class:"card-footer text-end"},k=["disabled"],q={key:1},T={key:0,class:"alert alert-success"},J={class:"alert-heading"},_={key:0},S=Object(i["j"])("Go to Terms & Definitions"),H={key:1},G=Object(i["j"])("Go to map"),M={key:1,class:"alert alert-warning"},z={class:"alert-heading"},I={key:0},A=Object(i["j"])("Go to Terms & Definitions"),C={key:1},D=Object(i["j"])("Go to Definition door"),Q={key:2,class:"alert alert-danger"},R={class:"alert-heading"},N={key:0},B=Object(i["j"])("Go to Terms & Definitions"),E={key:1},F=Object(i["j"])("Go to Definition door"),P={props:{item:Object,section:String},setup:function(e){var t=e,n=new c.a.Renderer,s=n.link;n.link=function(e,t,i){var a=e.startsWith("".concat(location.protocol,"//").concat(location.hostname)),o=s.call(n,e,t,i);return a?o:o.replace(/^<a /,'<a target="_blank" ')};var a=Object(i["I"])(t),r=a.item,l=a.section,P=Object(o["b"])(),L=function(e){return P.getters.selectedAnswer(e.id)},W=P.getters.getMaxQuestions(l.value),X=function(e,t){return 1==e.value?1==L(t)["selected"]?"success":"outline-success":0==e.value?0==L(t)["selected"]?"danger":"outline-danger":void 0},Y=function(e,t){return P.dispatch("addAnswer",{item:e,answer:t})},U=function(){return P.commit("updateQuestionNumber",l.value)},V=function(e){return P.getters.getScore(e)},K=[{text:"True",value:!0},{text:"False",value:!1}];return function(e,t){var s=Object(i["F"])("router-link");return Object(i["J"])(r)?(Object(i["y"])(),Object(i["g"])("div",u,[Object(i["h"])("div",f,[Object(i["h"])("div",b," Question "+Object(i["H"])(Object(i["J"])(r).number)+" of "+Object(i["H"])(Object(i["J"])(W)),1),Object(i["h"])("div",h,[Object(i["h"])("p",m,Object(i["H"])(Object(i["J"])(r).question),1),L(Object(i["J"])(r))?(Object(i["y"])(),Object(i["g"])("div",{key:0,class:"collapse",id:"explain",innerHTML:Object(i["J"])(c.a)(Object(i["J"])(r).explanation,{renderer:Object(i["J"])(n)})},null,8,p)):Object(i["f"])("",!0),Object(i["h"])("div",g,[Object(i["h"])("div",j,[(Object(i["y"])(),Object(i["g"])(i["a"],null,Object(i["E"])(K,(function(e){return Object(i["h"])("button",{class:Object(i["q"])(["btn","btn-"+X(e,Object(i["J"])(r))]),key:e.value,disabled:!!L(Object(i["J"])(r)),onClick:Object(i["O"])((function(t){return Y(Object(i["J"])(r),e.value)}),["stop"])},Object(i["H"])(e.text),11,O)})),64))]),L(Object(i["J"])(r))?(Object(i["y"])(),Object(i["g"])(i["a"],{key:0},[L(Object(i["J"])(r))["correct"]?(Object(i["y"])(),Object(i["g"])("span",y," Correct! ")):(Object(i["y"])(),Object(i["g"])("span",v," Incorrect! "))],64)):Object(i["f"])("",!0),Object(i["k"])(i["b"],{name:"fade"},{default:Object(i["M"])((function(){return[L(Object(i["J"])(r))?(Object(i["y"])(),Object(i["g"])("button",x," Explain")):Object(i["f"])("",!0)]})),_:1})])]),Object(i["h"])("div",w,[Object(i["h"])("button",{class:"btn btn-outline-secondary",disabled:!L(Object(i["J"])(r)),onClick:t[0]||(t[0]=Object(i["O"])((function(e){return U()}),["stop"]))}," Next ⮕",8,k)])])])):(Object(i["y"])(),Object(i["g"])("div",q,[V(Object(i["J"])(l))>75?(Object(i["y"])(),Object(i["g"])("div",T,[Object(i["h"])("h4",J,"Score: "+Object(i["H"])(V(Object(i["J"])(l)))+"%",1),Object(i["h"])("p",null,Object(i["H"])(Object(i["J"])(d.a).quiz_results.good),1),"definitions"===Object(i["J"])(l)?(Object(i["y"])(),Object(i["g"])("div",_,[Object(i["k"])(s,{class:"btn btn-secondary",to:"/terms-and-definitions"},{default:Object(i["M"])((function(){return[S]})),_:1})])):(Object(i["y"])(),Object(i["g"])("div",H,[Object(i["k"])(s,{class:"btn btn-secondary",to:"/"},{default:Object(i["M"])((function(){return[G]})),_:1})]))])):V(Object(i["J"])(l))>50?(Object(i["y"])(),Object(i["g"])("div",M,[Object(i["h"])("h4",z,"Score: "+Object(i["H"])(V(Object(i["J"])(l)))+"%",1),Object(i["h"])("p",null,Object(i["H"])(Object(i["J"])(d.a).quiz_results.average),1),"definitions"===Object(i["J"])(l)?(Object(i["y"])(),Object(i["g"])("div",I,[Object(i["k"])(s,{class:"btn btn-secondary",to:"/terms-and-definitions"},{default:Object(i["M"])((function(){return[A]})),_:1})])):(Object(i["y"])(),Object(i["g"])("div",C,[Object(i["k"])(s,{class:"btn btn-secondary",to:"/definition-door"},{default:Object(i["M"])((function(){return[D]})),_:1})]))])):(Object(i["y"])(),Object(i["g"])("div",Q,[Object(i["h"])("h4",R,"Score: "+Object(i["H"])(V(Object(i["J"])(l)))+"%",1),Object(i["h"])("p",null,Object(i["H"])(Object(i["J"])(d.a).quiz_results.bad),1),"definitions"===Object(i["J"])(l)?(Object(i["y"])(),Object(i["g"])("div",N,[Object(i["k"])(s,{class:"btn btn-secondary",to:"/terms-and-definitions"},{default:Object(i["M"])((function(){return[B]})),_:1})])):(Object(i["y"])(),Object(i["g"])("div",E,[Object(i["k"])(s,{class:"btn btn-secondary",to:"/definition-door"},{default:Object(i["M"])((function(){return[F]})),_:1})]))]))]))}}};const L=P;var W=L,X={props:{section:String},setup:function(e){var t=e,n=Object(o["b"])(),s=Object(i["I"])(t),r=s.section,c=a.a[r.value].title,l=1,d=a.a[r.value].questions.map((function(e){return e.number=l++,e}));n.commit("setNumberOfQuestions",{section:r.value,length:d.length});var u=function(){return n.getters.currentQuestionNumber(r.value)},f=function(e){return d.find((function(t){return t.number===e}))};return function(e,t){return Object(i["y"])(),Object(i["g"])(i["a"],null,[Object(i["h"])("h4",null,Object(i["H"])(Object(i["J"])(c)),1),Object(i["k"])(i["b"],{name:"fade"},{default:Object(i["M"])((function(){return[Object(i["k"])(W,{section:Object(i["J"])(r),item:f(u())},null,8,["section","item"])]})),_:1})],64)}}};n("8c06");const Y=X;var U=Y,V=function(e){return Object(i["B"])("data-v-17249e7d"),e=e(),Object(i["z"])(),e},K={class:"container-fluid py-4"},Z={class:"row justify-content-md-center"},$={class:"col-md-6"},ee=Object(i["j"])("Quiz "),te=["disabled","onClick"],ne=V((function(){return Object(i["h"])("i",{class:"bi-recycle"},null,-1)})),ie=Object(i["j"])(" Reset quiz "),se=[ne,ie],ae={setup:function(e){var t=Object(o["b"])(),n=Object(i["c"])((function(){return t.getters.totalAnswered})),s=function(e){return t.getters.quizAnswered(e)},a=function(){return t.commit("resetQuiz")};return function(e,t){return Object(i["y"])(),Object(i["g"])("div",K,[Object(i["h"])("div",Z,[Object(i["h"])("div",$,[Object(i["h"])("h1",null,[ee,Object(i["h"])("button",{class:"btn btn-outline-secondary float-end",disabled:!Object(i["J"])(n),onClick:Object(i["O"])(a,["stop"])},se,8,te)]),Object(i["k"])(U,{section:"definitions"}),s("definitions")?(Object(i["y"])(),Object(i["e"])(U,{key:0,section:"relevance"})):Object(i["f"])("",!0)])])])}}},oe=(n("3499"),n("6b0d")),re=n.n(oe);const ce=re()(ae,[["__scopeId","data-v-17249e7d"]]);t["default"]=ce},3499:function(e,t,n){"use strict";n("8fad")},6422:function(e,t){e.exports={definitions:{title:"What are the definitions for sex and gender?",questions:[{id:"definitions-q-1",question:"Sex and gender are always the same thing.",correct_answer:!1,explanation:"This is false. Sex refers to sets of biological traits of people and animals. It is associated with physical differences in chromosomes, gene-expression, hormone levels/functions and reproductive and sexual anatomy. It is often divided into males and females, while gender refers to a more complex interplay between socially constructed roles, behaviors, expressions and identities of girls, women, men, boys and gender diverse people. They are not the same, but they can interact with each other."},{id:"definitions-q-2",question:"The term “sex” should not be used in the context of research as it means sexual intercourse.",correct_answer:!1,explanation:"This is false. Sex can mean sexual intercourse or it can mean the biological differences between males and females. The fact that it has two meanings should never be the argument to avoid sex-sensitive research or reporting on sex differences, or replacing “sex” with the term “gender”."},{id:"definitions-q-3",question:"Sex refers to biological attributes in humans and animals, while gender refers to socially constructed roles, behaviors, expressions and identities.",correct_answer:!0,explanation:"This is true. Sex refers to sets of biological traits of people and animals. It is associated with physical differences inchromosomes, gene-expression, hormone levels/functions and reproductive and sexual anatomy. It is often divided into males and females, while gender refers to a more complex interplay between socially constructed roles, behaviors, expressions and identities of girls, women, men, boys and gender diverse people."},{id:"definitions-q-4",question:"Gender refers to biological attributes in humans and animals, while sex refers to socially constructed roles, behaviors, expressions and identities.",correct_answer:!1,explanation:"This is false. Gender refers to a complex interplay of identities and expectations associated with a girl, woman, boy, man, or gender-diverse person."},{id:"definitions-q-5",question:"Sex and gender are two separate dimensions that do not influence each other.",correct_answer:!1,explanation:"This is false. Although there are two difference definitions for sex an gender, they can interact and influence with each other. For example, sex can influence gene-expression. Gene-expression is also influenced by epigenetic regulation, which can be changed by certain lifestyle choices such as smoking. The behavior of smoking is influenced by gender roles in society (gender), which thereby via epigenetic regulation can influence gene-expression (sex)."},{id:"definitions-q-6",question:"Sex is always defined as sex assigned at birth.",correct_answer:!1,explanation:"This is false. Sex refers to the biological attributes in humans and animals and can be divided differently depending on the situation. Sex can also be defined based on chromosomes(XX/XY), which can differ from sex defined at birth due to mutations in the SRY gene (development of external genitalia). In public health and clinical research, sex is often defined as sex assigned at birth, but be aware that other options are possible."},{id:"definitions-q-7",question:"Taking a sex- and gender-based approach in research is beneficial for men, women, and gender-diverse people.",correct_answer:!0,explanation:"This is true. Research best tailored to their target population gives the most precise knowledge."},{id:"definitions-q-8",question:"Gender is a concept that cannot be objectively measured.",correct_answer:!1,explanation:"This is false. Gender questionnaires and indexes to measure gender exist, and this is an area that is continuing to develop. Note that which concept of gender you focus on (e.g., gender identity vs. gender expression) will influence which empirical measurement you want to use."}]},relevance:{title:"What are the relevance of accounting for sex/gender in biomedical and health research?",questions:[{id:"relevance-q-1",question:"Taking a sex-specific approach leads to discrimination",correct_answer:!1,explanation:"This is false. By accounting for sex in biomedical and health research, scientists are contributing for a more equal/balanced healthcare, also improving the rigor, reproducibility and generalization of science. Taking an approach of equity-based health care (recognizing that not everybody benefits from the same care) will help avoid discrimination."},{id:"relevance-q-2",question:"Performing sex-specific research costs more money",correct_answer:!1,explanation:"This is false. In the short term, it may be more costly, however, not accounting for sex differences along the different research phases can lead to a failure in the efficacy of treatment/healthcare in the long term, which costs more money. To illustrate, performing sex-specific analysis on the side effects of the COVID vaccination during the clinical trials stage could have avoided the surprise of increased side effects among women compared to men. The latter costs much more money."},{id:"relevance-q-3",question:"Gender does not apply directly to animals",correct_answer:!0,explanation:"This is true. Gender is defined as socially constructed roles, behaviours, expressions and identities from girls, women, boys, men and gender-diverse people. This definition does not directly apply to animals since they do not have such a societal environment as humans do."},{id:"relevance-q-4",question:"Female inclusion in animal experiments increase variability",correct_answer:!1,explanation:"This is false. That was a misconception common across the scientific community, which was based on the hypothesis that there would be greater sex hormone fluctuation in females due to the estrous cycle (Prendergast, Onishi et al. 2014, Becker, Prendergast et al. 2016, Beery 2018). It turns out males tend to have higher variation, which can be linked to external stressors related to the expression of dominance and power dynamics inherent to males."},{id:"relevance-q-5",question:"Sex awareness is unimportant to in vitro studies",correct_answer:!1,explanation:"This is false. Depending on what cell types used for in vitro studies (primary cells, cell lines), different details might need to be taken in consideration. Until recently, the importance of knowing the sex of cells being used has been overlooked. Resources on Analyzing Sex in Tissues and Cells can be found here [Analyzing Sex in Tissues and Cells](https://genderedinnovations.stanford.edu/methods/tissues.html)."},{id:"relevance-q-6",question:"Excluding women from clinical studies is always necessary to protect their fertility",correct_answer:!1,explanation:"This is false. This was a common misunderstanding for clinical studies in the past decades. However, by excluding women from clinical studies there is an increased risk on fertility since these side effects will not be discovered during clinical trials before going to the market. Additionally, intentionally excluding women from clinical trials without allowing them the opportunity to make an informed decision themselves does not respect the autonomy of women to make decisions regarding their own bodies."},{id:"relevance-q-7",question:"Reporting sex differences should only be mentioned when significant",correct_answer:!1,explanation:"This is false. Mentioning that no sex differences were observed is also relevant, as it will inform whether or not future studies are needed to investigate sex differences."},{id:"relevance-q-8",question:"Patient gender influences the treatment efficiency",correct_answer:!0,explanation:"This is true. Gender can influence treatment adherence and side effects due to differences in roles, stressors, help-seeking behaviours, supports, etc."},{id:"relevance-q-9",question:"Healthcare professional gender does not influence patient care",correct_answer:!1,explanation:"This is false. The gender of the healthcare profession can have a great influence on patient care in multiple dimensions, including how the patient perceives care, the type of complaints shared with professionals (https://www.ntvg.nl/artikelen/mannelijke-vrouwelijke-huisarts/abstract), diagnostic decision-making, and willingness of patients to see their provider for certain concerns."}]}}},"7db0":function(e,t,n){"use strict";var i=n("23e7"),s=n("b727").find,a=n("44d2"),o="find",r=!0;o in[]&&Array(1)[o]((function(){r=!1})),i({target:"Array",proto:!0,forced:r},{find:function(e){return s(this,e,arguments.length>1?arguments[1]:void 0)}}),a(o)},"857a":function(e,t,n){var i=n("e330"),s=n("1d80"),a=n("577e"),o=/"/g,r=i("".replace);e.exports=function(e,t,n,i){var c=a(s(e)),l="<"+t;return""!==n&&(l+=" "+n+'="'+r(a(i),o,"&quot;")+'"'),l+">"+c+"</"+t+">"}},"8c06":function(e,t,n){"use strict";n("0da3")},"8fad":function(e,t,n){},9911:function(e,t,n){"use strict";var i=n("23e7"),s=n("857a"),a=n("af03");i({target:"String",proto:!0,forced:a("link")},{link:function(e){return s(this,"a","href",e)}})},"99af":function(e,t,n){"use strict";var i=n("23e7"),s=n("da84"),a=n("d039"),o=n("e8b5"),r=n("861d"),c=n("7b0b"),l=n("07fa"),d=n("8418"),u=n("65f0"),f=n("1dde"),b=n("b622"),h=n("2d00"),m=b("isConcatSpreadable"),p=9007199254740991,g="Maximum allowed index exceeded",j=s.TypeError,O=h>=51||!a((function(){var e=[];return e[m]=!1,e.concat()[0]!==e})),y=f("concat"),v=function(e){if(!r(e))return!1;var t=e[m];return void 0!==t?!!t:o(e)},x=!O||!y;i({target:"Array",proto:!0,forced:x},{concat:function(e){var t,n,i,s,a,o=c(this),r=u(o,0),f=0;for(t=-1,i=arguments.length;t<i;t++)if(a=-1===t?o:arguments[t],v(a)){if(s=l(a),f+s>p)throw j(g);for(n=0;n<s;n++,f++)n in a&&d(r,f,a[n])}else{if(f>=p)throw j(g);d(r,f++,a)}return r.length=f,r}})},af03:function(e,t,n){var i=n("d039");e.exports=function(e){return i((function(){var t=""[e]('"');return t!==t.toLowerCase()||t.split('"').length>3}))}}}]);
//# sourceMappingURL=chunk-d846650e.0401444e.js.map